STEFAN DJOKIC

IT SOFTWARE ENGINEER ♥ NIS, 18000, SERBIA

• DETAILS •

Lole Stojanovica 28 Nis, 18000 Serbia <u>stefandjokic0407@gmail.com</u>

SKILLS

JavaScript

TypeScript

Node.js

React

Angular

Vue

MySQL

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

HTML & CSS

jQuery

HTML5

Bootstrap

PHP

Laravel

Wordpress

Python

Django

Flask

C#.NET

ASP.NET

ASP.NET MVC

Git

Docker

PROFILE

As a full-stack software engineer, I work closely together with Fortune 1000 enterprises to enhance their multi-lingual digital marketing and customer experience capabilities through our creative, strategic, technical, and operational services.

I strive to embody the values of loyalty, reliability, and authenticity, and I strongly believe in helping others achieve success. This is why I see projects through to the end and believe in not only creating beautiful software but also reliable software that reflects the client's brand and is easy to use so that it does not detract from the user experience.

- Back-end experience: .Net, PHP, Node.js, Electron.js
- Front-end experience: Angular, React, Vue.js
- Mobile App Development: React Native, Ionic
- Cloud Solutions Architect and DevOps(AWS, Firebase, Digital Ocean)

Your dream is my Mission!

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Engineer at Ingsoftware

August 2013 — July 2017

- Architect greenfield React / TypeScript / Redux application built with Gatsby and Next.js.
- Build a component library and implement design system created by UX/UI team.
- Help design content marketing strategy to attract dev ops specialists to Datree.io site.
- Write technical articles on Git, Node.js, DevOps, CI/CD, etc. as part of content marketing strategy.

.NET Developer at EXLRT

July 2017 — November 2020

- Full-stack development of design- and developer-oriented design product similar to Webflow using TypeScript, JavaScript, React, .NET Core, ASP.NET, C#, and Google Firebase
- Built abstract Angular UI components used in product and released open-source, e.g. tool-tip, scrolling, drop-down components
- Led three-engineer team through the development of mobile React data analytics the product when the original development team failed to meet requirements and deadlines.

Full Stack Engineer at Self-employed

January 2021 — Present

EDUCATION

Faculty of Electronic Engineering, University of Nis

Computer Engineering.

Gimnazija "Svetozar Markovic"

Computer Science